<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Text on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/tags/text/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Text on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/tags/text/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>County Limerick Landscape Improvisation Series</title>
      <link>https://example.org/art/landseries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/art/landseries/</guid>
      <description>Sound, Video, Photography, Sizes &amp;amp; Durations variable (2023-ongoing)&#xA;This work is an ongoing engagement with rural Limerick landscapes, combining deep listening, improvised sound-making, field recording and photography/videography. I perform this ritual with voice and electronics in local landscapes of varying land use (including peat bogs, industrial plants, dairy farmland, quarries, commercial forestry plantations), weaving with their sonic ecologies. I document this ritual with sound and video recording, and I document the landscapes with medium format photography.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERRA: Digital Ephemera from DoneDeal</title>
      <link>https://example.org/art/terra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/art/terra/</guid>
      <description>Self-published artist book, 60 pages&#xA;TERRA is a personal exploration of the image culture of &amp;lsquo;Ireland&amp;rsquo;s largest motor and classifieds website&amp;rsquo; DoneDeal.ie. As the author becomes engrossed by found imagery of cars, farm machinery, animals and land for sale – themes of rural ireland, agriculture, landscape and regional identity transpire. Given some attention, DoneDeal emerges as an intriguing living document of rural Ireland, as depicted incidentally by its own inhabitants. The publication has been stocked in The Library Project, Dublin, as well as visiting Tsundoku Art Book Fair (Dublin), DISTRO (Cavan Arts Festival), Limerick Zine Fest, Rebel Reads (Cork) and The Ecliptic Newsstand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stare at the Landscape Until Time Becomes Liquid</title>
      <link>https://example.org/art/stare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/art/stare/</guid>
      <description>Single channel video loop with sound (63mins), website-based text, and QR code installation&#xA;&amp;lsquo;Stare at the Landscape’ is a multimedia meditation on landscape – our relationship with it, the memory embodied in it, and the futurity potential in it. The work features a 63 minute single channel video of Limerick landscapes shot over a 15-month period, sound, and a web-based stream-of-consciousness text piece which viewers can access through their own devices using a QR code.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
